Wake up America, smell the decay Corporate vultures circling their prey The Department of Education bids drift away Billionaires calling all the shots today Tests were burnt, teachers purged Indolence raised, all is submerged A calculated plan they finally unleashed To keep the masses coming on their knees
Agitation's on the chomping block.
Puff it over once and find it's stock.
Tearing down what we built up.
I'm there, Doug, you jerk, so ain't bankrupt.
Hey, hey, dumbed down.
Hey, hey, sold out.
Billionaires with their twisted schemes Dismantling schools for profit dreams Children left behind, can't compete While other nations search ahead, we retreat They cut the fun, we cut the facts A generation's future under attack Critical thinking becomes a crime As we watch our country steeply twine
Agitation's on the chopping blot Puppet of our lives, a planet stock Tearing down what we build up On Merida's future, going bankrupt I, I, I, dumbed down I, sold out
Thief and maxi when ignorance reign A population they can't and easily contain No facts, no science, just propaganda flows A calculated plan that nobody knows While slick schools shuddered, privatized aim The wealthy get choices, the rest feel the pain Techboes and tyrants console what we learn While textbooks and truth get thrown into burns Education's on the chopping block
Profitable on the private stock Tearing down what we built but A merit of future going bankrupt Fight back!
Rise up!
Fight back!
Stand up!
Our children deserve more than their creed Knowledge is power we desperately need